Once again, we will be filming on location with the cooperation of Yukai Resort, Gero, and Nagaraku.
Thank you very much.
It has begun. Hachamichan Academy.
This will be the last time for the junior high school trip.
I'm sad.
It was so much fun.
Now, we will take a stroll in this hot spring resort town for the last time.
Let's take a leisurely stroll.
There is a river here, and the Hida River is connected to it.
You should see the clarity of the water.
Isn't it amazing?
It really is.
Just take a walk.
You want to swim, don't you?
It's not safe.
Resist the urge.
I'll just hang out, you can go swimming.
I'll get serious.
Well, I'm going to go for a stroll.
I'm off.
Kinkong, kankong.
There's something in there.
Twilight.
What's that look? Who is it?
Charles Chaplin.
Chaplin.
Chaplin, you know.
The Chaplin, right?
The movie.
With the hat.
Yes, I know.
What's the matter?
Well, Hou-san, I'll get it for you.
Thank you.
I'll make it look like I'm parenting a child.
Shoulder massage.
How does that feel?
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Yes, it does.
How do you take it off?
Oh, like that? No way.
Oh, my God! That's a lot of pressure.
You're an amazing guy.
Here you go. Cheese.
It's funny, isn't it?
I got it!
Let's all sit down next to each other like this.
Thank you for your time.
I'm sorry to have disturbed you.
Excuse me, excuse me, excuse me.
Okay, where should we go?
Oh, yummy!
Hidagyu buns!
I found it!
You must have one of these!
Hida Beef buns!
Well, you know, there are a lot of pork buns like this, but you wouldn't think it's a cow, would you?
Yes, I do!
I'm so happy!
What does it taste like?
I want to eat it! I want some!
Where do they sell it?
Here? Inside?
Oh, it's so cute!
I didn't know they made so many Salbobos. Isn't it cute?
A big Salvovo.
Look! Let's take a picture!
It looks like it has goliaths.
Can I take a picture of you?
Please do. Please take a picture.
Same pose as Salvobo.
Thank you very much.
Yes!
Look at that! It's a little light. It says "fortune" on it.
Good!
Now I feel secure.
We'll be fine in the future. We are.
It's about time.
Excuse me. Can I have two Hiragyu Manju, please?
Yes.
Thank you very much.
Let's eat outside.
We'll eat Hirayu Man.
The skin is firm and hard.
Let's eat outside.
Delicious!
Strong taste
It's like sukiyaki all wrapped up!
Miso?
Is there miso?
But the meat tastes amazing.
Meaty.
That's what I expect from Hidan-yu!
The skin is firm.
Delicious!Delicious.
Even the Salvobo shrine is here.
I didn't know there was such a shrine.
You know...
They love you so much.
Big guy.
God of longevity.
I'm counting on you.
I want to live a long time.
Emma here...
She paints her own face.
That's right.
She learned how to do it.
The reason she doesn't have a face is...
The reason she doesn't have a face is because it reflects the way she looks right now.
The face you see depends on how you're feeling at the time.
Like, when I'm sad, I look sad.
But this god of longevity...
What's with the beard?
Eyebrows?
Eyebrows? Beard?
Beard?
I have something.
But he's got a turtle, so it's either a beard or a mustache.
I guess.
What is it?
Gray hair.
I'll take care of it.
Please take care of it.
I'll hang it in my car from now on
Please take care of it
You all have an incredible amount of work to do.
Emma.
They love you.
Ah!
It's Mr. Ebisu.
Prosperous business
Yellow-green.
Hey!
Spring!
It's spring.
But it's spring, too, because we have fish.
Yeah, right.
Spring!
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Sarbobo shrine is nice.
It's a big one.
A Sarbobo shrine.
I'd be surprised if people from overseas came here.
Hmmm...
What the hell is this?
What kind of doll is this?
You've been around a lot, haven't you?
Yes, I feel like I know a lot of vomit already.
You know, we've been to a lot of places.
Yeah, well, we went to Takayama the first day.
We really enjoyed this area.
It was a lot of fun.
I love shoe trips!
The pictures, the pictures, the pictures!
The purpose of this trip was to take pictures that would look good.
So I'll just show you the last picture.
Okay.
Here's the last photo.
There were so many good pictures, I got lost in them.
I had a lot of really good memories!
Thank you very much for the junior high school trip!
Thank you very much!
It's time for Orca News!
We, Team Killer Whale, are now on our 3 Green Live Tour!
We are touring in various places!
We will of course be performing live, but we will also be holding special events, so please come and see us!
Please come and see us!
And, what's more...
This summer, on July 22nd, we will be holding a "Shachi-sama" at Nagoya Castle.
We will be holding a "Killer Whale" event at Nagoya Castle!
Yay! It's Killer Whale!
It's our one-man show for the summer.
Last year, we came back after a long absence.
We'll be performing outdoors, at Nagoya Castle
The place where it all began.
Yes, Nagoya Castle is where I made my debut on the street.
the place of our memories and the killer whales!
It's so much fun!
Just thinking about it makes me emo.
Yes, it's so bad!
And I'm feeling it, too.
After all, it's really hot in Nagoya in the summer
I want to do a live show that won't let the heat get the better of me.
Please come to Nagoya Castle on July 22nd!
We're looking forward to seeing you there!
That's all for now.